{
    "subject": "resource/Birth_of_a_Notion_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/series",
    "object": "resource/Looney_Tunes",
    "human_readable": "The film 'Birth of a Notion' is part of Looney Tunes series.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9788655042648315,
            "question": "Is 'Birth of a Notion' part of the Looney Tunes series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8115628361701965,
            "question": "Name one film from the Looney Tunes series."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7716675996780396,
            "question": "What is the name of the film featuring 'Birth of a Notion'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6999991536140442,
            "question": "To which series does the film 'Birth of a Notion' belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6190253496170044,
            "question": "Can you describe the humor often found in Looney Tunes films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6180946826934814,
            "question": "What is a common theme found in Looney Tunes films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5517640709877014,
            "question": "Who are some popular characters in the Looney Tunes series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5029820203781128,
            "question": "What kind of animated series is Looney Tunes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43088120222091675,
            "question": "When was the first Looney Tunes film released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03633381798863411,
            "question": "Name another film featuring popular characters like Bugs Bunny and Daffy Duck."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film 'Birth of a Notion' is part of Looney Tunes series.",
            "html": "dbpedia_713_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the first Looney Tunes film released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_713_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of animated series is Looney Tunes?",
            "html": "dbpedia_713_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some popular characters in the Looney Tunes series?",
            "html": "dbpedia_713_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_713_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_713_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_713_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_713_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_713_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_713_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_713_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_713_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_713_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_713_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that \"The Birth of a Notion\" is a Looney Tunes short film, which supports the statement that the film 'Birth of a Notion' is part of the Looney Tunes series."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}